Marlon Riggs Papers, 1957-1994 M1759
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Audio Visual
  - Subseries 2: Ethnic Notions
    - Ethnic Notions: National Archives, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 143, Folder 91)
    - Ethnic Notions: Tape 92 and 96 - Film Footage, Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 143, Folder 92)
      tape No. 92: Clips of KKK march and dancing/watermelon eating - also tape no.96: UC, Berkeley Library clips
    - Ethnic Notions: B. Christian, 1986; Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 143, Folder 94)
      Interview with Barbara Christian (transferred onto Digibeta and DVD in 2007)
    - Ethnic Notions: UC, Berkeley Library, 1986; Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 143, Folder 95)
      Clips from UC, Berkeley Library and civil rights books
    - Ethnic Notions: UC, Berkeley Library, 1986; Video: (Box 143, Folder 96)
      See Tape No.92
    - Ethnic Notions: Library of Congress, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 143, Folder 97)
      Library of Congress stills (KQED shoot)
    - Ethnic Notions: Emperor Jones, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 143, Folder 98)
      Emperor Jones
    - Ethnic Notions: Audio Transfer, 1986; Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 143, Folder 100)
      Audio transfer from 1/2inch tape - from 05 Nov
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #4, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 4)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 19 and 20 - S.F. Performing Arts Archive
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #15, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 5)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 42 and 43 - Faulkner Collection
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #6, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 6)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 23 and 24 - S.F. Performing Arts Archive
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #7, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 7)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 25 and 26 - Library of Congress
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #17, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 7)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 46 and 47 - Larry Levine Interview and Faulkner Collection
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #10, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 10)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 31 and 32 - Library of Congress
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #11, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 11)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 33 and 34 - Library of Congress
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #12, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 12)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 35 and 36 - Library of Congress and National Museum of American History
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #13, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 13)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 37-39 - National Museum of American History and Harvard Theatre Collection
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #19, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 19)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 51-53 - Faulkner Collection and Interview with Faulkner
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #21, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 144, Folder 21)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 56-58 - Faulkner Collection and Interview with Barbara Christian
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #22, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 22)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 59 and 60 - Bancroft Library Collection
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #26, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 26)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 65 - Black and White Films
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #27, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 27)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 66 - Animation
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #28, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 28)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 67 - Animation
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #30, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 30)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 69 - LoC short silent films
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #31, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 31)
      Music Source Reels 1 & 2 - from 13 Mar 1986
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #32, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 32)
      Music Source Reel 3 - from 13 Mar 1986
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #34, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 34)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 73-75 - Interviews with Bea Richards and Carlton Moss
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #35, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 35)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 76 and 96 - Carlton Moss Interview and UC, Berkeley Library
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #36, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 36)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 78 and 79 - Shots of Faulkner collection and interview withGeorge Frederickson
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #37, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 145, Folder 37)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 80 and 81 - Interviews with Frederickson, Dundes and Erskine Peters
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #38, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 146, Folder 38)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 82 and 83 - Interviews with Erskine Peters and Cita Cook, also Harper's Weekly (1860s) and U.C. Library/Faulkner Collection
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #39, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 146, Folder 39)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 84 and 85 - UC, Berkeley Library/Faulkner Collection and Barbara Doyle Interview
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #40, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 146, Folder 40)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 86 - UC, Berkeley Library/Faulkner Collection and Tape No. 90-92 - National Archives tapes
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #41, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 146, Folder 41)
      Corresponding with tape no.913a - Library of Congress: Good & Bad, Ambrose & Steve in count, Laughing Coon, Mammy's Shufflin' dance, and Insect Powder Agent - also Emperor Jones
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #42, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 146, Folder 42)
      Corresponding with Tape No. 88 and 89 - Judge Priest and Little Colonel
    - Ethnic Notions Worktape #55, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 146, Folder 55)
      KQED Master - Dub of Master online Audio Worktape
    - Window Dub #67, 1986; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 146, Folder 67)
    - Library of Congress recording, 1986; Audio: 1/4inch reel; 2500ft (Box 153, Folder 913)
      Library of Congress: Good & Bad, Ambrose & Steve in count, Laughing Coon, Mammy's Shufflin' dance, and Insect Powder Agent
    - Ethnic Notions: Music Source Reel 1, 1986; Audio: 1/4inch reel (Box 153, Folder 914)
      Recorded 13 Mar 1986
    - Ethnic Notions: Music Source Reel 2, 1986; Audio: 1/4inch reel (Box 153, Folder 915)
    - Ethnic Notions: Music Source Reel 3, 1986; Audio: 1/4inch reel (Box 153, Folder 916)
    - Ethnic Notions: Original Music, 1986; Audio:: 1/4inch reel (Box 153, Folder 918)
      Master Audio Tape - Mary Watkins composer
    - Ethnic Notions: Voice over, 1986; Audio:: 1/4inch reel (Box 153, Folder 919)
      Reel 1 - outs - Nov 1986
    - Ethnic Notions: Voice Master Original, 1986; Audio: 1/4inch reel (Box 153, Folder 920)
      Voice Master - Nov 1986
    - Ethnic Notions: Voice Master Dub, 1986; Audio: 1/4inch reel (Box 153, Folder 921)
      Time coded
    - Ethnic Notions: Voice Over, 1986; Audio: 1/4inch reel (Box 153, Folder 922)
      Janets Outs
    - Ethnic Notions: Test Tape, Audio:; 1/4inch reel (Box 174, Folder 923)
      Test Tape - Blank (apart from tones at start)
    - Unknown content, Audio:; 1/4inch reel (Box 174, Folder 924)
      Unknown content
    - Ethnic Notions: Soundtracks, 1984; Audio:; 1/4inch reel (Box 174, Folder 925)
      Soundtracks circa 1984
    - Tape 1 Side 1, Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 1200ft (Box 174, Folder 926)
    - Tape 2 Side 1, Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 1200ft (Box 174, Folder 927)
    - Tape 3, Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 1200ft (Box 174, Folder 928)
    - Unknown content, Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 900ft (Box 174, Folder 929)
      Blank
    - Minstrel Skit, Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 900ft (Box 174, Folder 930)
      Voice Overs - Minstrel Skit and Rascist
    - Janet Keller, 1985; Audio: 1/4 inch reel; 900ft (Box 174, Folder 931)
      Audio of Janet Keller - from 05 Jun 1985
    - Ethnic Notions: Assembly #2 Pt 2, Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 180, Folder 204)
      B & C
    - Ethnic Notions: Film Fund Sample, Video: Umatic (Box 180, Folder 210)
      Film Fund Sample - 2 Tracks
    - Ethnic Notions: Assembly tape, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 180, Folder 217)
      B&C
    - Ethnic Notions: Work in Progress, Video: Umatic; 50mins (Box 180, Folder 221)
      B&C - narrated by Marlon Riggs
    - B & C, Video: Umatic (Box 180, Folder 222)
      Ethnic Notions - B&C
    - B & C, Video: Umatic (Box 180, Folder 224)
    - Ethnic Notions: Final Cut, Video: Umatic (Box 180, Folder 225)
      Final Cut Off-Line with original record window
    - Ethnic Notions: Final Cut, Video: Umatic (Box 180, Folder 225)
      Final Cut Off-Line with original record window - unmixed
    - Ethnic Notions: Rough Cut Excerpts, Video: Umatic (Box 180, Folder 302)
      KQED rough cut excerpts
    - Ethnic Notions: Music, Video: Umatic (Box 181, Folder 901)
      Ethnic Notions Music - Source Reel #1 (copy of 1/4inch CTC Master)
    - Ethnic Notions: Music, Video: Umatic (Box 181, Folder 902)
      Ethnic Notions Music - Source Reel #2 (copy of 1/4inch CTC Master)
    - Ethnic Notions: Music, Video: Umatic (Box 181, Folder 903)
      Ethnic Notions Music - Source Reel #3 (copy of 1/4inch CTC Master)
    - Ethnic Notions: Music & Skits, Video: Umatic (Box 181, Folder 904)
      Ethnic Notions Music - Source Reel #4 (copy of 1/4inch CTC Master) from Library of Congress: Good & Bad, Ambrose & Steve in count, Laughing Coon, Mammy's Shufflin' dance, and Insect Powder Agent
    - Ethnic Notions: PI Dub, Video: Umatic (Box 181, Folder 905)
      9mins
    - Ethnic Notions: Audio announce, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 181, Folder 906)
      window dub
    - Ethnic Notions: Over Easy, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 181, Folder 907)
      Johnson-Bruce Family Lifestyle 26 Sep 1980 Produced by Joan Saffa, 8mins
    - Ethnic Notions: Original Music - Digital Master, Video: BetaMax; 90mins (Box 181, Folder 908)
      1986
    - Ethnic Notions: KQED Master, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 181, Folder 909)
      Ethnic Notions - KQED Version - Master
    - Ethnic Notions Work in Progress, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 181, Folder 910)
    - Ethnic Notions Work in Progress, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 181, Folder 911)
    - Ethnic Notions, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 182, Folder 1000)
      Packaged version of Ethnic Notions - 7 copies (2 enclosed cellophane wrap)
    - Ethnic Notions, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 182, Folder 1001)
      For Academy Use
    - Ethnic Notions, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 182, Folder 1002)
      CORI Film Distributors
    - Ethnic Notions, 1996; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 182, Folder 1003)
      Copy sent to the 1st Seoul Documentary Film Festival 1996
    - Ethnic Notions, 1989; Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 182, Folder 1004)
      PBS version airdate: 02/01/1989
    - Ethnic Notions, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 182, Folder 1005)
      Final version of Ethnic Notions
    - Ethnic Notions, 1987; Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 182, Folder 1006)
      Excerpts from Ethnic Notions (1987)
    - Ethnic Notions: Pat Turner, Video: DVD;; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 40)
    - Ethnic Notions: Pat Turner/Faulkner, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 41)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner Collection, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 42)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner Collection, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 43)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner/Levine, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 44)
    - Ethnic Notions: Larry Levine, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 45)
    - Ethnic Notions: Levine/Faulkner, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 46)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner Collection, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 47)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner Collection, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 48)
    - Ethnic Notions: Kids with toys/Faulkner, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 49)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner Collection, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 50)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner Collection, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 51)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner collection, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 52)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner Interview, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 53)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner Interview 2, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 54)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner collection, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 55)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner/Christian, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 56)
    - Ethnic Notions: Barbara Christian, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 57)
    - Ethnic Notions: Barbara Christian, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 58)
    - Ethnic Notions: Bancroft Library Collection, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 59)
    - Ethnic Notions: Bea Richards, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 73)
    - Ethnic Notions: Richards/Moss, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 74)
    - Ethnic Notions: Carlton Moss, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 75)
    - Ethnic Notions: Carlton Moss, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 76)
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner Collection, Video: DVD (Box 231, Folder 78)
      Transfer by BAVC in 2007 - 2 DVD copies
    - Ethnic Notions: Faulkner/Frederickson, Video: DVD (Box 231, Folder 79)
    - Ethnic Notions: Interviews, Video: DVD (Box 231, Folder 80)
    - Ethnic Notions: Peters, Video: DVD (Box 231, Folder 81)
    - Ethnic Notions: Peters/Cook, Video: DVD (Box 231, Folder 82)
    - Ethnic Notions: Cita Cook, Video: DVD (Box 231, Folder 83)
    - Ethnic Notions: UC, Berkeley/Doyle, Video: DVD (Box 231, Folder 85)
    - Ethnic Notions: Christian/UC, Berkeley, Video: DVD (Box 231, Folder 94)
      DVD copy of DB Master
    - Ethnic Notions: Assembly #2 Pt 2, Video: DVD; 20mins (Box 231, Folder 204)
    - Ethnic Notions: Assembly tape, Video: DVD; 60mins (Box 231, Folder 217)
    - Ethnic Notions: Work in Progress, Video: DVD; 50mins (Box 231, Folder 221)
    - Ethnic Notions: Tapes 41-51 - extra copies - not labelled, Video: DVD (Box 231, Folder 4151)
      7 DVDs with slo mo of still images showing stereotypes of black people. 1 DVD has children shown playing with toys and 3 DVDs feature an interview with Larry Levine as well as pictures
    - Ethnic Notions, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 232, Folder 52)
      California Newsreel Version
    - Ethnic Notions - Portraits of Prejudice, Video: 1inch reel (Box 234, Folder 912)
      PBS Version
    - Edit Master, Video: 1inch reel (Box 234, Folder 1010)
      NTSC
    - Ethnic Notions - PAL Version, 1989; Video: 1inch reel (Box 234, Folder 1011)
      Icarus Films - from 10 Feb 1989
    - Ethnic Notions - PAL Version, 1988; Video: 1inch reel (Box 234, Folder 1012)
      ITN version from 29 Dec 1988
    - ABC in Dixie - a Plantation Alphabet, 1986; Video: 1inch reel (Box 235, Folder 17)
      Special Effects - Motion Control Camera Original - no audio (29 Oct 1986)
    - Ethnic Notions: Topsy and Eva, Video: 1 inch open reel (Box 235, Folder 63)
    - Ethnic Notions - Master Tape, Video: 1inch reel (Box 235, Folder 1013)
    - Ethnic Notions - Master, Video: 1inch reel (Box 235, Folder 1014)
      Dub of Back Up
    - Ethnic Notions Pt 1, Video: 2inch reel (Box 236, Folder 1015)
    - Ethnic Notions Pt 2, Video: 2inch reel (Box 236, Folder 1016)
    - Ethnic Notions: VO/Music, 1986; Audio: 1/2inch reel (Box 240, Folder 100)
      Ch1 - Voice Over, Ch2 - Music - from 04 Nov 1986
    - Ethnic Notions: Voices, 1986; Audio: 1/2inch reel (Box 240, Folder 101)
      Voices - From 13 Oct 1986
    - Ethnic Notions: Original Music, Audio: 1/2inch reel (Box 240, Folder 915)
      8-track unmixed master tape of music - Mary Watkins composer
  - Subseries 3: Tongues Untied
    - Berlin '90, 1990; Video: 8mm; 60mins (Flat-box 21, Folder 1)
    - AFI/LA Tongues Premiere 30 Oct 1989, Video: 8mm; 30mins (Flat-box 21, Folder 2)
    - Tongues Untied - State Edition, 1991; Audio:: Cassette Tape; 10mins (Flat-box 25, Folder 22)
      Michigan Public Radio News report about a Detroit TV station not showing 'Tongues Untied' and the protests surrounding this action - with telephone interviews with the manager of the Detroit TV station and Marlon Riggs (Doug Johnson reporter - from 16 Jul 1991)
    - Tongues Untied - Essex Hemphill, Audio:: Cassette Tape (Flat-box 25, Folder 23)
      excerpts for MTR Productions - 'Brother to Brother' (Side A only)
    - Tongues Untied - Essex Hemphill, Audio:: Cassette Tape; 90mins (Flat-box 25, Folder 24)
      Brother to Brother - Words from the Heart
    - Tongues Untied - Festival at the Lake, 1988; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Recorded on 04 Jun 1988
    - Tongues Untied - Festival at the Lake, 1988; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Tongues Untied - Festival at the Lake, 1988; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Recorded on 04 Jun 1988 - Voice over Alan Miller
    - Tongues Untied - Cabel's Reef, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Other countries - Cabel's Reef
    - Tongues Untied - Cabel's Reef, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Tongues Untied - Cabel's Reef, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Tongues Untied - Beach House, 1988; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 7)
      BGMU - 1988
    - Tongues Untied - Dinner, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Other Countries - By the pier
    - Tongues Untied - Voguing, 1988; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Voguing/Jesse in Park/Letter - recorded Aug 1988
    - Tongues Untied - Jesse/Jackson, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Jesse and Reginald Jackson
    - Tongues Untied - Jackson/Poetry/ Colin, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 11)
      Reginald Jackson/ NY Poetry Reading/Colin at home
    - Tongues Untied - March on Mayors, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 12)
      Oakland April 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Candlelight March, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 13)
      Mugging/Candlelight March - Lake Merritt 27 May 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Slides, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 13)
      Recorded on 14 Jun 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Slides, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Tongues Untied - Slides, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Tongues Untied - Slides, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 16)
      Recorded on 15 Jun 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Slides, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Tongues Untied - Slides, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Tongues Untied - Drag Queens, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 19)
      Moon/Drag Queens recorded on 19 Jun 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Necklace of lights, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 20)
      Moon/Necklace of Lights - recorded on 19 Jun 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Bella's, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 21)
      Recorded on 21 Jun 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Bella's, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Tongues Untied - Bella's, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Tongues Untied - Bella's/Essex, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Tongues Untied - Essex Hemphill, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 25)
      Essex Hemphill and voices - recorded on 23 Jun 1989
    - Tongues Untied - NY Parade, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 26)
      Recorded on 25 Jun 1989
    - Tongues Untied - NY Parade, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Tongues Untied - D.C. Poets, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 28)
      D.C. Poets/Essex and Co. recorded on 28 Jun 1989
    - Tongues Untied - D.C. Poets, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 29)
      D.C. Poets - recorded on 30 Jun 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Poetry, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 30)
      Poetry from Essex Hemphill, Larry Duckette, Wayson Jones and D.C. Poets - recorded on 30 Aug 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Obituaries, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 31)
      Go Home' - recorded on 07 Jul 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Preacher, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 28, Folder 32)
      Buppie
    - Tongues Untied - Sylvester, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 33)
      Sylvester James - Disco Diva
    - Tongues Untied - Faces, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 34)
      Buppie/faces/PC
    - Eddie Murphy/School Daze, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 35)
      Eddie Murphy 'Raw' and School Daze
    - Tongues Untied - Faces, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 36)
      Faces/PC/Alex
    - Tongues Untied - Alex, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 37)
      Recorded 14 Jul 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Doowop, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 38)
      Recorded 15 Jul 1989
    - Tongues Untied - 'Turn me around', 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 39)
      Turn me around', Snap and Electric Boogie Dance - Recorded 15 Jul 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Bro to Bro, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 40)
      Headphones/Bro to Bro/Initiation scenes - recorded 16 Jul 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Finger Snaps, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 41)
      Recorded on 27 Jul 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Bro to Bro, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 42)
      Bro to Bro/Holiday, Simone, Flack/Music House songs
    - Tongues Untied - Basketball/Bridge Castro, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 44)
      Recorded 26 Aug 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Conga drums, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 45)
      Conga drums/ Josh Piagentini - recorded on 27 Aug 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Brian and Bernard, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 46)
      recorded on 27 Aug 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Lovers Quarrel, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 47)
      Michael Cole/Dancers - recorded on 27 Aug 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Dancing, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 48)
      Recorded on 30 Aug 1989
    - Tongues Untied - MTR in Black, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 49)
      Marlon T Riggs in Black - recorded 04 Sep 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Punk - Terry, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 50)
      recorded on 07 Aug 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Terry - close, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Tongues Untied - Close - Snap - Racists, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 52)
      with voice over of Alan Miller and Marlon Riggs - recorded on 07 Aug 1989
    - Tongues Untied - KTVU News Tape, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 29, Folder 53)
      KTVU news tape
    - Tongues Untied - KTVU News Tape, Video: Umatic; 10mins (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Tongues Untied - Folsom St Fair, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 55)
      recorded on 24 Sep 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Stills, 1989; Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 56)
      Stills of Marlon as a boy. Castro sequence and BGM photos - recorded on 26 Sep. 1989
    - Tongues Untied - Sounds, 1989; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 29, Folder 57)
      Sounds from Berke - karate, snaps, clock, whip, wings, sword, heartbeat, glass breaking, and rap song
    - Tongues Untied - Miscellaneous sound, 1989; Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 29, Folder 58)
      Miscellaneous sound
    - Tongues Untied - African American Freedom Day, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 59)
      NYC
    - Tongues Untied - African American Freedom Day, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 60)
      NYC - parade
    - Tongues Untied - Pick up, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 29, Folder 61)
      Classified pick up, T-shirt, my pick up
    - Tongues Untied - Submaster A, Video: 1inch reel (Box 31, Folder 908)
      Submaster A
    - Tongues Untied - Submaster B, Video: 1inch reel (Box 31, Folder 909)
      Submaster B
    - Tongues Untied - Dub, Video: 1inch reel (Box 31, Folder 910)
      Dub